对于ForecastFragment类里的问题
For the solution within ForecastFragment, we
我们实现了继承自AsyncTask类的FetchWeatherTask类。
implemented FetchWeatherTask, which extends AsyncTask. The generics
这里的泛型我们只用了Void，在这里是没问题的。然后在doInBackground()方法里
we use are just Void, and this is fine for now. Then within the doInBackground
把之前网络部分的代码片段复制进来
method, we copied our networking codes snippet,
大体是相同的，除了在
here. It's the same, except [INAUDIBLE] in
某些情况下我们返回一个null
certain cases we return null instead of
而不是将包含天气预报信息的JSON字符串赋值为null
setting the forecast JSON string to be null.
之前，代码是在onCreateView()方法中的
Previously, the code was in onCreateView, which expected us
这个方法需要我们扩展并返回一个View对象，所以有必要运行到
inflate and return a View. So it's important that it got
下面这些代码
to the rest of the code. Even if there was an
即使在网络部分的代码中报错。现在网络部分的代码在
error in the networking code. Now that the networking code is in
AsyncTask类里面，doInBackground()方法中也没有什么东西
AsyncTask, there's really nothing that comes after this in
紧随其后。所以遇到报错就立即返回
the doInBackground method. So it's fine to just bail early
也没有关系。另外对于我们的日志信息
whenever there's an error. Also know that for our log messages,
我们在类的最上面定义了一个LOG_TAG常量。
we've defined a log tag constant at the top of this task.
这个LOG_TAG被定义为FetchWeatherTask类的名字
This log tag is defined to be the name of the FetchWeatherTask class. The
我们这么做而不是
reason we use this syntax instead
声明一个FetchWeatherTask的字符串，是因为
of declaring a string FetchWeatherTask, it because
我们希望这个常量能一直和类名保持一致。如果你重命名了这个类
we want these two to be in sync. If you ever rename the
那么这儿将抛出一个异常，除非你同样修改了这儿。
class then it will throw an exception unless you also update it here.